<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Q-LINKED</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Q-LINKED</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Cornerstones of Trust: A Philosophy of Compliance, Prudence, and Openness in Technology</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/fourth-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/fourth-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After painting a grand vision, articulating a profound philosophy, and designing an intricate mechanism, we must now answer a series of the most serious and practical questions: How will all of this be implemented through solid, reliable, and responsible engineering? Are you capable of achieving it?&#xA;This article is our answer. It will clearly display the bridge from Q-Linked&amp;rsquo;s concept to reality, and our philosophy as builders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;first-principle-compliance-first-embrace-regulation&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;First Principle: Compliance First, Embrace Regulation&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#first-principle-compliance-first-embrace-regulation&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before discussing any technical details, we must first clarify our position: &lt;strong&gt;We are a Chinese company serving China&amp;rsquo;s real economy, and all our technical architecture and business models are built with compliance with national laws and regulations as the highest premise.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Identity: The Social Contract that Carries Trust</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/third-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/third-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/posts/third-post/Digital-Identity.jpeg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After exploring the necessity and philosophical foundation for rebuilding trust, we must answer a core question: what will be the carrier for this weighty, computable trust?&#xA;The answer is: a new form of &lt;strong&gt;digital identity&lt;/strong&gt;.&#xA;We must redefine &amp;ldquo;digital identity.&amp;rdquo; It should no longer be the disposable &amp;ldquo;accounts&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;avatars&amp;rdquo; we register on various platforms. It must become the sole vessel of our digital persona, a dynamic and unique &lt;strong&gt;social contract&lt;/strong&gt; that records all our actions and carries all our credit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Alchemy of Trust: From Human Covenants to the Bedrock of Digital Civilization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/posts/second-post/The-Alchemy-of-Trust.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Trust is the lubricant that allows the intricate machinery of human society to operate. It is also its most ancient, most powerful, yet most ambiguous force.&#xA;Why can a single promise lead a woman to wait eighteen years for a man far away? Why can trust in one person allow us to place our lives in the hands of a surgeon we&amp;rsquo;ve never met? Why can faith in a cause inspire countless ancestors to sacrifice their lives in pursuit of a distant ideal?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why We Need a Third Way: Rekindling the Embers of Digital Civilization from the Fog of Capital</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/en/posts/first-post/the-third-way.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every great migration in human history is accompanied by the reconstruction of order. From the physical to the digital world, we are experiencing a civilizational leap of unprecedented scale. We have discovered this vast new continent and built unparalleled prosperity, yet we have also fallen into a profound &amp;ldquo;Columbus&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma&amp;rdquo;: we possess the technology to connect everything, but we do not know how to establish a truly fair and trustworthy civilization upon this land.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
